Savana, can we talk?
He really looks familiar.
He went viral last week.
They say people were furious at him
because he's a land grabber.
Liam Herrera, land grabber.
Mom, why do many people seem
to be obsessed with Savana?
It feels like I've known her for a long time.
I'm so fond of her.
She's so familiar to me.
Savana, I want you
to meet Liam, my boyfriend.
I sympathize with the poor.
So I can't understand how you could do that
to the residents of Verde Village.
I'm sorry for whatever our company did.
You don't need to explain.
I just want to call you out
because what you did is wrong.
So I'm giving you a second chance, Liam.
Are you reinstating me at Casa Fuerte?
No, but I will assign you
to one of the other companies...
Blacksmith Productions.
Auntie, have some water.
Son!
Liam.
Goodness...
Congratulations!
Via told me that you'll make a film
with Savana in Blacksmith.
Let me tag along when you film it, okay?
- Sure, Mom.
- Okay.
Sorry, I told her before you could.
It's good news anyway.
It's okay.
I'll just get the other food in the kitchen.
Son...
I'm so happy for you.
You can finally fulfill your dream
of making a film, right?
Mom, it's still Vergil's project.
I can't own it.
Come on.
It's only for now.
You can make the film you want next time.
You can make it according to your taste.
Promise me you'll do your best.
Don't waste this opportunity.
You've wasted a lot of time already.
You're good at construction,
but your heart isn't there.
Mom, everything I do is for you.
So I promise that wherever I get assigned,
be it in the construction
or the production company,
I'll do everything to make you proud.
You're just saying that
to make me feel better.
- No.
- No?
Oh, boy!
[Batang Bilibid]
[Boy Backflip, by Ramon dela Peña]
[Pretty Boy, by Ramon dela Peña]
[.45 Caliber]
[My Teacher, My Idol]
So you're the core team
of the Tristan-Savana project?
Yes. And you are?
I am William Herrera.
I'll be supervising this project
on behalf of my brother, Vergil Herrera.
So he's our boss.
- I'm Megan Marcelo.
- Hi.
The executive producer of Idol.
And this is our writer, Leroy del Mundo.
And our creative assistant,
Ms. Deedee Fernandez.
- Hello.
This is my executive assistant, Borj Rodrigo.
Sir, have some snacks.
- Have a seat, Sir.
- Thank you.
- Deedee.
Yes.
Here.
Can I get some now?
- I'll have some of this.
- Yes, go ahead, Sir.
It's good, Sir.
It's my son's favorite.
- Oh, really?
- Yes.
Do you have a spoon?
Boss.
Thank you.
Can we start the meeting?
Okay, any updates?
Leroy is finalizing the script, Sir.
And this is the casting for VLH's approval.
Boss Bro.
You don't know anyone, right?
Guys, let's take a picture for documentation.
Okay?
Hashtag, Tristan-Savana Project.
Smile!
There. One more. Candid.
Candid.
Okay.
There you go.
Boss Bro, don't you really know anyone?
Me, too.
But it's okay.
Let's fake it till we make it.
Sir, they appear in drama series.
- Is that so?
- Yes.
And the others are theater actors.
We'll just do our research.
I'll take a look at it.
Yeah.
By the way, guys,
Congressman Ramon asked
if we could tweak the script
to make it different from his previous movie.
He thinks the stories are too similar.
Okay, I can do it on my own.
Bro, you probably haven't heard,
but Sir Liam has a degree
in Creative Writing.
My name is Leroy.
And no. I'm not asking.
Hey. What are you doing?
I will consult with you, Sir Liam,
if I need to.
Okay.
Sir, please eat.
Sure.
Savana, let's have a picture together!
Deedee, right?
Yes, Sir?
Deedee, I need you to do something.
Smile!
There you go. Okay.
Thank you!
- Thank you!
- One more, here.
Here, too.
- That's enough.
- That's okay.
Oh, sorry, Sir.
Thank you.
Odet, stay here for now.
Okay, sure.
Savana.
Have a seat.
Water? Juice? Brandy?
Let's talk.
Yes, Savana, we're talking.
I'll be honest with you.
I don't want to work with your brother.
Liam?
Yes.
Well, we have a common ground.
You're not the only one who doesn't like him.
Great.
I want a new creative manager for my film.
Savana, listen.
I didn't hire him.
It was the company president's decision.
But you run Blacksmith, right?
Liam is non-negotiable, unfortunately.
Then find a new actress.
Savana!
Wait.
Calm down, okay?
Why don't you like Liam?
Our grandfather is still in jail.
He didn't do anything wrong.
He only wants Casa Fuerte
to take responsibility
for everything they did to Verde Village.
A lot of us lost our jobs and houses.
The Herreras took everything from us!
They took everything from us!
When I started in show business,
I promised only one thing...
And that is to help the oppressed.
I will use my position and influence
to become their voice.
Blacksmith has nothing to do with
whatever Liam did in Casa Fuerte.
No, Vergil.
You're a family.
All your companies benefit
from the profits of Casa Fuerte.
So, then... what do you want?
I don't want to work with Liam Herrera.
That's what I want.
Hey. Pretty girl, what are you doing there?
I want a selfie with Ms. Savana.
- You want a picture, too?
- Yes.
Okay, I'll tell her later.
- Later.
- Okay.
Leave for now.
Okay.
What are they talking about?
Sir, Savana wants you out of the project.
Savana, wait.
What do you need this time?
I just want to know why you're furious at me.
I thought I already made it clear.
Do I have to remind you, Liam Herrera,
how many lives got ruined
because of your project in Casa Fuerte?
Liam, they are humans.
They are humans,
not insects you can expel out of their homes.
Look...
Whatever it is I have done...
I'm owning up to my mistakes.
No, Liam.
What is an apology without accountability?
How can you say you own up to your mistakes
when someone else suffers because of you?
You know what, Savana...
Like I said,
Liam is a non-negotiable
to my father and Congressman Ramon.
But as the saying goes,
keep your friends close
and your enemies closer.
What do you mean?
Well, I think it's better that Liam is here,
and not in Casa Fuerte.
He won't be able to work on his pet project
in Verde Village.
And while he's here,
we can make his life a living hell,
until he gives up.
[National Police]
[Sto. Cristo Police District]
- Nestor Bartolome.
- Sir.
You're free to go.
What?
Sir...
Who bailed me out?
The case against you has been dropped.
Grandpa?
Grandson!
Thank you for dropping the case
against my grandfather.
Son, why are you thanking them?
They are the reason
why almost all of Verde Village was wiped out.
That's enough, Grandpa.
What matters now is you're free.
I'm really sorry.
What do you mean free?
It's a good thing
that I attacked this scumbag.
If not, our house would have been demolished.
Grandpa, please calm down.
Please, hear my son out.
Mister...
First of all, I apologize
for what I did to Verde Village.
Yes.
I desired a good life.
But I didn't realize
that it was at your expense
and the residents of Verde Village.
I know that I can't bring back
the lives and crops that were lost,
no matter what I do.
But I promise you,
I will do everything
to find you a new home and livelihood.
For you and the rest of Verde Village.
Thank you.
A lot of politicians have promised us
the same thing.
I don't expect that you can do that.
But I believe
that your intentions are pure, kid.
So I forgive you.
I hope you can also forgive me
for what I did to you.
Thank you so much.
I'm so proud of you, son.
I never thought that you could do that
because of everything that happened.
I'm glad someone knocked some sense into me.
You know...
Even if you take the wrong path,
your heart will lead you to the right way.
But Mom,
I'm worried that the livelihood project
I'm planning for Verde Village
will deplete my life savings.
You'll earn it again.
You're good.
But what if there's an emergency?
What if you get sick again?
Sir, Ma'am, good morning.
Good morning.
Son, there's always a way.
And if it's already your time,
you can't do anything about it.
And...
from what I saw,
I think my job as a mother is done.
Mom, don't talk like that.
I'm serious.
Just pray, son.
Keep on praying.
Miss Savana, have some palabok.
Okay, sequence 17.
Exterior. Bar. Night.
Cindy is being harassed by some men.
Chito will arrive
like a knight in shining armor.
How dare you!
The woman is helpless,
yet you are harassing her?
The man harassing the woman will laugh.
He will glare at Chito.
A fight ensues.
This is good.
I like how it was written.
And the fight scenes are also good.
Poor Cindy.
Luckily, Chito's there.
Helpless Cindy thanks her savior.
- Luckily...
- Stop!
This is not right.
Huh?
The scene is good.
I'm going to save you, right?
That's the point.
That's the problem.
That's what sells.
This will be among your list of hit movies.
Helpless woman saved by her leading man.
That's a formula.
I need no saving.
We, women, need no saving.
How this movie is written...
should also show women
who can defend themselves.
Right!
Women empowerment.
I also agree.
Usually, Gen Z, like me,
can identify more with strong,
independent female characters.
Then talk to VLH, if that's what you want.
Actually, I already talked to him.
He approved my request, too.
Wait.
So you want to discard the whole material
to accommodate Miss Savana's request?
You need to think about my welfare, too.
So you want me to start from scratch again?
New story, new characterization,
new screenplay.
You need to pay me again.
But this is the same project, Leroy.
You were already paid for it.
This is not the same project, Megan.
In principle,
this is already a different film.
I understand that, Leroy.
I don't think they can do it.
Maybe you should get a new team, Liam.
What I mean is...
creative work should not be charity work.
So Megan,
please prepare the budget for Leroy.
And you have a strong point, too, Savana.
Women empowerment...
gender equality.
You're right.
So, Leroy,
are you still willing to write
for an additional half
of your professional fee?
I'll take care of the other half.
I will co-write with you.
It's true.
It seems that in this story,
you're not the princess
who always needs saving.
You're a queen, and you needed no saving.
[Care in Paradise Orphanage]
- Good evening.
- Good evening, everyone.
Good evening, Mother.
I'm sorry for coming late.
This is my fifth ribbon-cutting ceremony
for the day.
It's okay, Congressman. No problem.
Thank you so much.
It's an honor to give public service
to those who need it.
Especially to children
who are close to my heart.
You know...
I grew up on the streets, too.
I lost my parents at an early age.
I worked hard until I reached this position
where I can finally give back
and share my luck with others.
Thank you so much for inviting me here.
We should thank you
for the building you put up for the kids.
Thank you so much.
You're welcome. You're welcome, Mother.
Thank you so much again.
Thank you.
Here it is, Congressman.
- Thank you.
Congressman, for you.
Thank you so much.
Thank you.
Thank you all.
Congressman?
Congressman, we need to go.
People ask, who do I wake up for?
But here I am, asking...
Who do I stay up late for?
I never imagined
I would be a passionate writer again.
All I remember is the time
when I was
with my wife, Joyce, and my son, Dex.
It seems so long ago.
I always bear this in mind.
That I need to be strong.
Because when you love and like what you do,
you have a clear reason to fight.
Where am I?
Let me go.
Why am I tied up?
Who are you?
Congressman?
Congressman. Congressman, I'm glad you came.
Hey!
Untie me.
The congressman is here now.
Keep quiet.
Congressman, are they your men?
I think they took the wrong guy.
I said, keep quiet!
Congressman...
They didn't make a mistake.
I ordered them to bring you here.
Why?
Congressman, I'm loyal to you.
That's why you trust me, right?
That's my mistake.
I trusted you fully.
I gave you complete trust!
Where's the rest of the money
from the transaction in Magallanes?
What?
That's 20 million pesos.
Do you think I forgot about it?
- Huh?
- Congressman...
Congressman, I don't know
what you're talking about.
I don't know anything about that...
I don't know anything.
Congressman?
Congressman, what are you going to do?
Congressman.
Congressman, what's that?
What are you going to do with me?
Congressman!
Congressman, I don't know
what you're talking about.
Congressman, I'm begging you!
Congressman, have mercy.
Congressman.
Congressman!
Hold on, Congressman!
Wait!
My mother got sick.
No. No. It was my grandfather.
Congressman, I will pay you back.
There's still money left.
I will have my wife get it.
Congressman, please stop.
Congressman.
- Congressman.
- That's all I want to hear.
For you to tell the truth.
But I know where you live.
I'll let my men get the money.
I don't want to bother you.
It would be too much.
Congressman, leave my family alone.
Congressman, keep my family out of this!
Congressman!
Congressman, no!
I'm begging you, Congressman! No!
Congressman.
Now you know what will happen...
if you do the same thing.
Sir?
Sorry, but...
Unbelievable. She still doesn't like it?
I'm sorry, Megan.
It's okay, Sir.
I saw the effort you made the whole night.
It's not a common sight here in Blacksmith.
We haven't seen someone work hard
as much as you do in a long while.
Oh, boy.
I should thank you instead.
You stayed with me the whole night.
We have to, Sir.
Single mom representative.
And, Leroy...
he has so many debts to pay.
He's the breadwinner of his family.
Deedee, on the other hand,
is a working student.
Career-oriented.
It's nice because even if they're sleeping,
their passion is very much awake.
The passion of this creative team.
Megan...
Don't worry.
I'll work on this.
And let them sleep for now.
And maybe you should go home.
I'm sure your kid misses you already.
Yes, Sir.
By the way, where's Savana?
You were so good earlier.
Your scene with Savana was so great.
- You're very good in...
- Bye. Thank you so much.
I enjoyed the shoot today.
Take care.
- Bye.
- Bye!
Very good. You're so great. We'll meet again.
- Savana?
- When is your next filming schedule?
- Saturday.
- Saturday?
Can we set things straight?
What do you need this time, Liam?
What do you really want, Savana?
I already said it.
I want an empowered character.
Is what we wrote
not empowering enough for you?
We've addressed all your comments,
and all your requests already.
Something still seems wrong.
Wrong?
Savana, what don't you like about it?
Tell me what you don't like.
Or is it because you want your role
to become more relevant than Tristan's?
You.
You are what's wrong, Liam.
Isn't that clear to you?
I don't want to work with you.
See?
My team is having a hard time
because of your personal hatred.
You keep the project hanging.
Savana, don't you realize?
Everyone's job is affected because of you.
Megan...
Megan is supporting her kid's schooling.
Leroy is a breadwinner.
Deedee is saving up money for her tuition.
And you, you're toying with us.
Savana, you're so unprofessional.
I hope you feel guilty.
I'm sorry.
If you really hate me that much,
why did you accept this project?
Because I am bound by the contract.
How about you?
Why do you insist on writing a movie?
Because I wanted to be
given a second chance...
To prove that I could still do
what I really want.
To correct the mistakes I made.
Are we still talking about the script?
I've paid for it already.
And I know I will continue to pay for it
as long as I am trapped in this situation.
So if you're telling me
that you're trapped, Joyce...
I mean, Savana.
Let's work together to break free
and to create a decent output.
Okay, bye. Bye.
Bye, Auntie.
Okay, Savana, let's go home.
Savana?
Where is she going?
Savana!
Come back here.
- Savana.
- Hi, Savana!
- Hi, Chuchi.
Hey, there's Savana!
- So pretty.
- Hi, Savana!
How are you, MJ?
I'm okay.
- Hi, Savana.
- Hello.
Savana, please buy some of this.
Savana, buy from me, please.
I'll come back later. Make it good.
Yes, Ma'am.
Grandpa Nestor?
Savana!
I'm glad you came to visit.
How are you, Grandpa?
When did they let you out of jail?
Just the other day.
Liam dropped the case against me.
And not just that.
He gave the residents of Verde Village
a livelihood,
so we could start again.
- Hey, eat first.
- Yes, Ma'am.
- Dear, give her some.
- Here you go.
Okay, cook more of it.
Okay.
He really paid for it.
That scumbag did pay for it.
If you really are the reason
why I am here in this strange world,
I won't be tired of looking for you.
What magic did you bring into my life?
Is it really magic?
Why does it seem like a curse?
Mister?
Do you sell other antique typewriters
aside from the one on display?
What kind of typewriter are you looking for?
Something more rusty with a fading keyboard.
The one I have has rust and fading keyboard.
Maybe a little bigger than that.
Why don't you buy the one on display?
It's just the same.
I can't do that, Mister.
My life depends on
the typewriter I'm looking for.
Is that so?
You said life?
How much is it? A million?
More than that.
It has sentimental value.
Let me get your number,
so I can text you
if an old typewriter arrives.
Okay. Thank you so much.
Here you go.
Okay. I'll text you.
Thank you so much.
What brings you here?
Make it quick. I'm busy.
I know you don't want me here.
You're right.
- Brother...
- VLH.
I came here as your brother.
I brought this.
Resignation letter.
Irrevocable?
Yes.
Sir, I told her you're busy,
but Miss Savana wants to talk to you.
Of course, anytime.
Savana, what can I do for you?
Script, please.
- What's this?
- I'm going to be part of this film.
Well, if this is already okay with you,
I will now review it.
In the meantime, give me and Liam a minute
so we can talk about his resignation.
Bro, it's a prank!
Thank you so much for your time, Bro.
Thank you so much.
I think we should go, Miss Savana.
I'm excited about our look test.
Sure.
Bro!
Pest!
Thank you so much, Savana.
But what made you change your mind?
You, Liam.
Me?
Why me?
Because you're right.
Everyone deserves a second chance.
I know that you helped the residents
of Verde Village.
It's nothing.
What is an apology
without accountability, right?
I also want to apologize to you.
For what?
I just can't bear to see
people being oppressed.
Thank you so much, too, Savana.
Thank you for enlightening me.
Am I interrupting something?
Via.
Another day is not the same as the other day.
True queens fix each other's crowns.
I'm not sure about others, though.
Beware.
Miss Savana?
Let's go.
Okay. Please fix that.
Help!
Savana!
Sorry, why are you here?
This is my condo.
You almost got harmed, Savana.
Luckily, Liam and I passed by.
I'm sorry.
- What do you think, Boss Bro?
- I think they should end up together.
How, Liam?
Tell her everything he did wrong.
He'll suffer for it.
He'll take all the woman's anger.
The girl will see
how much effort the man puts
into changing his ways.
Oh my, crocodile!
Have you been here long?
Via...